<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<modDesc descVersion="94">
    <author>GMNGjoy</author>
    <version>1.0.8.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>Contract Boost</en>
        <de>Auftragssteigerung</de>
        <fr>Contrat Amélioré</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Boost your contracts by making more money, and allowing collection of the spoils!

Features:
- 50% more profit from every contract
- 10 max contracts
- 5 max contracts per type by default
- Allow setting a custom amount per type of contract
- 50 total contracts available
- Borrowed contract equipment comes with free fieldwork items to fill your tools
- Allow using swathing equipment on harvest contracts
- Allow collecting straw from harvest contracts
- Allow collecting grass from mowing contracts
- Allow collecting stones from plow, cultivate, and sowing contracts
- Allow collecting hay from tedding contracts
- Allow collecting straw bales from baling contracts
- Allow collecting wrapped silage bales from bale-wrapping contracts

All of the above settings can be modified in-game through the General Settings panel.

NOTE: Setting changes that may affect the reward or number of missions may *not* affect any already generated contracts.

GitHub link: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2
- Added safety check for custom maps that don't contain every type of contract

Changelog 1.1.0.0 (in development)
- User contributed translations: fr, cz, it, pl, ru, da
- Allow collecting hay from tedding contracts.
- Allow collecting straw bales from baling contracts.
- Allow collecting wrapped silage bales from bale-wrapping contracts.
- Support customizing of the number of contracts for each type of contract individually, with the ability to "disable" contract types you don't want to see.
- All settings previously in the configuration file can be set in the General Settings panel in-game.
- Configuration file in modSettings folder has been depreciated.
- New configuration file in savegame folder can only be manually edited while game is not running.
- Fixed baleMission setting to be perHa instead of perBale.
- Added cultivator to seeding missions, just in case you mess up.
- Rebuilt Settings to work with MP Syncronization :: Dedicated Server is the source of truth for settings, clients recieve settings on connect.
- Added feature to remove already added fill items when setting is switched off
- Added balancing feature to remove unwanted contracts when a maxPerType or customMaxPerType setting is SAVED. (note: contracts are not removed until game is saved).
- Added console command: cbDebugToggle to toggle debugMode.
- Added override to settings file only: enableInGameSettingsMenu, default: true
- Fixed collecting bales from baling & bale wrapping contracts in both SP & MP.
- Added setting to support custom or dynamically generated grass fields properly with contracts, which should prevent grass fields from getting plowed or cultivated.
- Added harvest settings (default: on) for the "new crops", "premium crops", "root crops", Sugarcane, and Cotton - to block those type of harvest contracts if you don't want them. 
]]></en>
        <de>
Hole mehr aus deinen Aufträgen heraus indem du mehr Geld bekommst und die Beute einsammeln kannst!

Features:
- 50% mehr Umsatz von jedem Auftrag
- Bis zu 10 angenommene Aufträge
- Standardmäßig maximal 5 Verträge pro Typ
- Anpassung einer individuellen Anzahl pro Vertragsart ermöglichen
- Bis zu 50 angebotene Aufträge
- Beim Mieten der Maschinen werden auch kostenlos Verbrauchsgüter zum Füllen der Geräte bereitgestellt
- Ernteaufträge können auch mit Schwadmähern durchgeführt werden
- Bei Ernteaufträgen kann das Stroh geborgen werden
- Bei Mähaufträgen kann das Gras gesammelt werden
- Bei Pflug-, Grubber- und Saatmissionen können Steine aufgesammelt werden

All diese Einstellungen können über eine XML Datei unter FarmingSimulator2025/modSettings/ContractBoost.xml angepasst werden

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2
- Sicherheitsüberprüfung für Karten hinzugefügt, die nicht alle Vertragsarten unterstützen
</de>
        <fr>
Augmentez vos revenus grâce à vos contrats et récupérez les ressources collectées !

Fonctionnalités :
- 50 % de profit supplémentaire pour chaque contrat
- Jusqu'à 10 contrats actifs
- Jusqu'à 5 contrats actifs par type (par défaut)
- Possibilité de définir un nombre personnalisé pour chaque type de contrat
- Jusqu'à 50 contrats disponibles au total
- Les équipements loués pour les contrats incluent gratuitement des consommables pour remplir vos outils
- Permet d'utiliser la coupe en andains lors des contrats de récolte
- Permet de collecter la paille lors des contrats de récolte
- Permet de collecter l'herbe lors des contrats de fauchage
- Permet de collecter les pierres lors des contrats de labourage, de travail des champs et d'ensemencement
- Permet de collecter le foin lors des contrats de fanage
- Permet de collecter des bottes de paille lors des contrats de mise en balles
- Permet de collecter des bottes d'ensilage lors des contrats d'enrubannage

Tous les paramètres ci-dessus peuvent être modifiés directement dans le panneau Paramètres généraux en jeu.

NOTE : Les modifications des paramètres qui influencent les récompenses ou le nombre de missions *n'affecteront pas* les contrats déjà générés.

Lien GitHub : https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2 :
- Ajout d'une vérification de sécurité pour les cartes personnalisées ne contenant pas tous les types de contrats

Changelog 1.1.0.0 :
- Traductions ajoutées par la communauté : fr, cz, it, pl, ru
- Permet de collecter le foin lors des contrats de fanage
- Permet de collecter des bottes de paille lors des contrats de mise en balles
- Permet de collecter des bottes d'ensilage lors des contrats d'enrubannage
- Support de la personnalisation du nombre de contrats pour chaque type individuellement, avec la possibilité de "désactiver" les types de contrats non souhaités
- Tous les paramètres précédemment dans le fichier de configuration sont désormais accessibles via le panneau Paramètres généraux en jeu
- Le fichier de configuration dans le dossier modSettings est obsolète
- Nouveau fichier de configuration dans le dossier savegame, éditable uniquement hors jeu
- Correction du paramètre des missions de balles pour qu'il soit défini par hectare au lieu de par balle.
- Ajout d'un cultivateur aux missions d'ensemencement, au cas où vous feriez une erreur.
- Correction d'un bug mineur lorsque le mode débogage est désactivé.
</fr>
        <it>
Aumenta i tuoi contratti guadagnando più soldi e raccogliendo i bottini!

Caratteristiche:
- 50% in più di profitto da ogni contratto
- 10 contratti massimi
- 5 contratti massimi per tipo per impostazione predefinita
- Consente di impostare una quantità personalizzata per tipo di contratto
- 50 contratti totali disponibili
- L'attrezzatura a noleggio per i contratti include gratuitamente articoli per il lavoro sul campo per riempire i tuoi strumenti
- Consente di utilizzare l'attrezzatura per la falciatura nei contratti di raccolta
- Consente di raccogliere la paglia dai contratti di raccolta
- Consente di raccogliere l'erba dai contratti di falciatura
- Consente di raccogliere pietre dai contratti di aratura, coltivazione e semina
- Consente di raccogliere il fieno dai contratti di giratura
- Consente di raccogliere balle di paglia dai contratti di pressatura
- Consente di raccogliere balle di insilato avvolte dai contratti di avvolgimento delle balle

Tutte le impostazioni sopra elencate possono essere modificate in gioco tramite il pannello Impostazioni Generali.

NOTA: Le modifiche alle impostazioni che possono influenzare la ricompensa o il numero di missioni *non* influenzeranno i contratti già generati.

Link GitHub: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2
- Aggiunto controllo di sicurezza per le mappe personalizzate che non contengono tutti i tipi di contratti

Changelog 1.1.0.0
- Traduzioni contribuite dagli utenti: fr, cz, it, pl, ru
- Consente di raccogliere il fieno dai contratti di giratura
- Consente di raccogliere balle di paglia dai contratti di pressatura
- Consente di raccogliere balle di insilato avvolte dai contratti di avvolgimento delle balle
- Supporta la personalizzazione del numero di contratti per ciascun tipo di contratto individualmente, con la possibilità di "disattivare" i tipi di contratti che non desideri vedere.
- Tutte le impostazioni precedentemente nel file di configurazione possono essere impostate nel pannello Impostazioni Generali in gioco.
- Il file di configurazione nella cartella modSettings è deprecato
- Nuovo file di configurazione nella cartella savegame modificabile solo mentre il gioco non è in esecuzione.
- Corretto il parametro della missione delle balle in modo che sia perHa anziché perBale
- Aggiunto coltivatore alle missioni di semina, nel caso facessi un errore
- Corretto un bug minore quando la modalità debug è disattivata.
</it>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_contractBoost.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractBoost.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/MissionBalance.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/MissionBorrow.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/MissionTools.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/MissionFields.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/Settings.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/SettingsChangeEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/SettingsManager.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/SettingsUI.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/lib/UIHelper.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n"/>
</modDesc>