<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>GMNGjoy</author>
    <version>1.0.0.2</version>
    <title>
        <en>Contract Boost</en>
        <de>Auftragssteigerung</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
Boost your contracts by making more money, and allowing collection of the spoils!

Features:
- 50% more profit from every contract
- 10 max contracts
- 5 max contracts per type
- 50 total contracts available
- Borrowed contract equipment comes with free fieldwork items to fill your tools
- Allow using swathing equipment on harvest missions
- Allow collecting straw from harvest missionss
- Allow collecting grass from mowing missions
- Allow collecting stones from plow, cultivate, and sowing missions

All of the above settings can be modified via an XML settings file at FarmingSimulator2025/modSettings/ContractBoost.xml

GitHub link: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2
- Added safety check for custom maps that don't contain every type of contract
</en>
        <de>
Hole mehr aus deinen Aufträgen heraus indem du mehr Geld bekommst und die Beute einsammeln kannst!

Features:
- 50% mehr Umsatz von jedem Auftrag
- Bis zu 10 angenommene Aufträge
- Bis zu 5 Aufträge pro Art
- Bis zu 50 angebotene Aufträge
- Beim Mieten der Maschinen werden auch kostenlos Verbrauchsgüter zum Füllen der Geräte bereitgestellt
- Ernteaufträge können auch mit Schwadmähern durchgeführt werden
- Bei Ernteaufträgen kann das Stroh geborgen werden
- Bei Mähaufträgen kann das Gras gesammelt werden
- Bei Pflug-, Grubber- und Saatmissionen können Steine aufgesammelt werden

All diese Einstellungen können über eine XML Datei unter FarmingSimulator2025/modSettings/ContractBoost.xml angepasst werden

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS25_ContractBoost

Changelog 1.0.0.2
- Sicherheitsüberprüfung für Karten hinzugefügt, die nicht alle Vertragsarten unterstützen
</de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_contractBoost.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractBoost.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>